Report Designer: AI-Powered Financial Report Generation
Creating a new report template in seconds
The workspace: Sections, Subsections, and AI Assistant
Sections organize your report — each can span multiple pages
Instructions tell the AI exactly what content to generate
AI generates content using real earnings data and transcripts
Subsections (A, B, C) stack vertically — add as many as needed
Preview shows how your report will look when exported
Natural language chat — ask the AI to modify your report
Build comprehensive reports with multiple sections
One-click export to professional PDF format
Report Designer: From data to insights in minutes